

# **MIGUEL TAFUR**

# UX/UI and Motion Graphics Designer

Porfolio (Behance) behance.net/migueltafmart

# ABOUT ME

BA of Design graduate based in Madrid, focused on graphic and interactive design. Experience as a volunteer; as the head of the department of an LGBTQ+ non-profit organization, two months as a intern in RTVE, the national television broadcast network, and six months as an intern in the digital marketing department in Grupo Anaya, a editorial group subsidiary of Hachette Book Group.

# JOB EXPERIENCE

#### Digital and graphic desing Internship in digital marketing

Grupo ANAYA, Madrid

November 2019 - April 2020

Videos and graphics for promotion in social media.

(After Effects, Adobe Premiere, Adobe Media Encoder, Illustrator)

Assistance in web development.(Adobe Dreamweaver, Atom)

SEO on Google.

Flyers and catalogs (BtB and BtC)

(Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator)

#### Motion graphics designer internship

RTVE. Madrid

July 2018 - August 2018

Introduction and continuity elements for the TV Show "Atención Obras"

(After Effects, Illustrator)

Promotion assets. (Adobe Premiere, Media Encoder, After Effects) (Adobe Premie-

re, Media Encoder, After Effects)

# **Graphic Designer**

Freelance, Madrid

2016 - Actualidad

Merchandise for the rugby team "TRC" (Illustrator)

Rugby team uniform for "Derecho Femenino UCM"

(Illustrator, Photoshop)

Branding and identity design for the "Not Fragile" Clothing brand.

(Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign)

Book cover of "Todos los Martes Fueron Tuyos" de Andrea Montero

Graphic Designer (Volunteer)

# COGAM, LGBTQ+ Non-profit, Madrid

March 2016 - Actualidad

Educacional divulgation content.

(InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator)

Presentation and graphic support for classroom activities.

(InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator)

Posters and flyers.

(InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator)

Branding and identity. (InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator)

# **EDUCATION**

MA in UX/UI Design Trazos\_

Currently Grad. 2021

Bootcamp FullStack Web Development The Bridge

Currently Grad. 2021

BA in Design Universidad Complutense de Madrid

2014 - 2020

# **SKILLS**

# Graphic Design:

Illustrator - Avanced Photoshop - Avanced InDesign - Avanced Lightroom - Avanced

#### Audiovisuales:

Premiere - Intermediate After Effects - Avanced Audition (Audio) - Intermediate Logic - Intermediate

# Web & App Development:

Android Studio - Begginer Dreamweaver - Intermediate Atom - Intermediate

# Coding Languages:

HTML5 - Intermediate CSS - Intermediate Javascript - Intermediate Java - Intermediate

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish - Native English - C1

Oxford International Academy London

# OTHER INTERESTS

Photography 2011-Videography 2017-Musical Production 2013-Lighting Design 2018-